# **ANUMIT JOOLOOR**

#### WordPress Developer

@ anumit@gmail.com

https://anumit-web.github.io/

Pleasanton, CA

## **SUMMARY**

A highly skilled and proficient WordPress developer with over twenty years of professional experience in all aspects of WordPress website and web solutions creation, including design, plug-ins, and implementation. Results-driven individual contributor with a successful track record in exceeding expectations for web development initiatives.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WORDPRESS DEVELOPER**

#### **OnSiteWP Arizona**

🛱 2016 - Present

Phoenix, AZ

OnSiteWP professional WordPress support services. It is based in Arizona.

- · Designed and developed client websites with WordPress
- · Backend support for firearms website
- · Migration of website to WordPress for a major drug maker
- Worked on payment interfaces for a veterans website
- · Optimized website loading time performance

#### Web Developer / WordPress / ERP Analyst / Freelancer

#### Cincinnati Children Hospital, State farm, Era with Tech

# 2014 - 2023 ♥ Cincinnati (OH), Bloomington (IL), US

I have worked on creating web solutions for hospital, insurance company, startups, higher education institution.

- Created web portal for doctors and nurses to view their information and manage their data
- Worked on enhancing website for the vendors for state farm company
- Working on creating web solutions for a medical startup

#### Web Developer / ERP Analyst

#### Lone Star College, Houston, Texas

苗 2011 - 2014 👂 Houston, TX

Lonestar college is based in Northen Houston area and is a community college serving students of greater Houston area.

- Created web portal for students, faculty, employees, vendors and baord members
- Designed students information portlets, employee pay, leave and absence portlets, vendor management web system and board members information charts

#### Web Developer / ERP Analyst

#### **HSBC Bank, Bear Sterns, Chicago colleges**

- · At HSBC bank created web portal for employees
- At Bear Sterns created web portal for employee systems
- At Chicago colleges worked on web based employee information system
- Installation of web platform on servers

## **SKILLS**

WordPress

Web Development

**PHP** 

HTML

**JavaScript** 

CSS

MySQL

MongoDB

### **EDUCATION**

## MS Computer Science

Indiana University Bloomington

**=** 2002 - 2004

GPA
3.81 / 4.0

## TRAINING/COURSES

#### **Certified Web Developer**

Portual

### **STRENGTHS**



#### **Online Comunication**

Effective online communication, present compelling messages in a one-way setting in order to be successful



#### **Time Managment**

Prioritize my tasks and efficiently organize everything to achieve my goals

### **LANGUAGES**

English

Native

